We were not ready for their divine judgment.
We were tested and almost everyone just…
failed.
Their dark mysticism shattered an era of enlightenment.
And ushered in the dusk of the 21st century.
Billions of lives were lost in a heartbeat.
Turned to ash and cast away in the wind.
Our soldiers were gone.
But our weapons kept fighting.
Driven by an enigma in the networks.
Their surviving forces waged a desperate crusade against the machines.
We became bystanders to a relentless war.
Now our world is an ever-twisting nightmare.
Hellish threats lurk in every whisper and shadow.
There is no glory.
Only survival.
Deliver us from this trial.
Reclaim our world.
For mankind.